for super delegate Tuesday I'm gonna
tell you why our governments are in no
way a solution to any of our problems so
regardless of who actually gets the
nomination let's change our world for
the better together ourselves instead of
leave it up to our governments here are
five reasons why our governments are in
no way capable of coming up with the
solutions to our complex problems one
all of our democracies are left versus
right
they are very divisive they are done in
a very rival risk win-lose way so even
if you do manage to get elected you have
generally around fifty percent of the
population who didn't even vote for you
who still represent and even are the
people who did vote for you you cannot
make all of them happy it is designed to
be divisive not to actually come up with
solutions that are going to make the
majority of people happy because you
can't make the majority of people happy
under the current system - they are if
they take a very long time to implement
any single solution it's designed that
it has to be this way they have to have
a test group they have to then roll it
out into a our sorry focus group and
then a test group and to see is this
actually a plan that works and because
of number two we get to number three
which is every solution they come up
with is extremely expensive compared to
what would be what a corporation would
come up with or at least they're
beholden to the marketplace
the government's usually use more labor
to come up with it and they have higher
wages and they take longer to implement
anything so because of that they come up
with very expensive solutions that take
a really long time to implement which
brings us to number four they only have
four years to implement it and see a
successful solution for their
constituents to feel it's a success so
that they will be reelected and so four
is kind of all about it's like that they
only have four years to implement it but
also that they have to make decisions to
be re-elected because if they're not the
next government is gonna come in and
undo everything they did so it's not
even permanent they spend a lot of time
and money coming up with
illusions that then are undone by the
next government and number five the
final reason they are in no way able to
clump these solutions is because they
don't have the information that is
required
they don't have information that is both
trustworthy and usable in all of the
areas they would need to have it in all
of the data all of the scientific data
the economic information that the
psychological needs of their
constituents they have to guess as to
what we need implement it make nobody
happy take a long time and a lot of
money to implement it so that was the
five reasons why governments aren't
going to create the solutions but good
news we are gonna create the solutions
together because we don't have those
problems we don't need to come up with a
win all solution for everybody in our
country just the people who want to be
part of that solution we can spend less
money less time coming up with them and
it can be a little bit for everyone
instead of our governments whatever they
do that is the crapshoot they have so on
this super delegate Tuesday how about
you vote for me instead hit the
subscribe button hit the little bell and
let's create a better world together
thanks